(Leonard:)Listen, I don't know if I can go
on the expedition.
- What?
- I don't think I can go to the North Pole.
(Sheldon:)Okay. Leonard, I know you're concerned
about disappointing me...
(Sheldon:)...I want you to take comfort
from the knowledge...
(Sheldon:)...that my expectations of you
are very low.
(Leonard:)Yeah, that's very comforting.
(Sheldon:)Comforting is a part of leadership.
(Sheldon:)It's not a part I care for
but such is my burden.
(Leonard:)Terrific. It's just that
I don't think Penny wants me to go.
(Sheldon:)Assuming that's a valid reason not to go,
which it isn't...
(Sheldon:)...how do you know this?
Did she say it?
(Leonard:)Not exactly.
(Leonard:)But she said she was gonna miss me
and she gave me this.
- What is it?
- It's a blanket with sleeves.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's clever.
(Sheldon:)Let me see if I understand this.
(Sheldon:)Her missing you,
is an emotional state you find desirable.